【血族】前情回顾
Previously on The Strain...
就像是死尸一样
Looks like a dead animal.
里面静静地坐着两百多个乘客
There have been 200 people sitting there silently,
-一点动静都没有 -我的天
- absolutely no movement. - Oh, my God...
-你看到了吗 -他们全都死了
- Are you seeing this? - They're all dead.
-没有挣扎的痕迹
- No signs of struggle. -
-发现幸存者了 -我以前见过这种疾病
- We've got survivors! - I've seen this disease before.
如果棺材还在你手里 他就没办法
If you have the coffin, then you still have him?
你必须在黎明前开过桥回到曼哈顿
You will cross the bridge back into Manhattan before daybreak.
他们会放你过去的
You will be let through.
封锁机场周边出口
Seal off the perimeter of the airport.
收到 我说了放行
Got it. I said let him through.
啊
Ah!
爸爸
我好冷啊
布鲁克林 红钩区 理查兹街
嗨 嗯哼
Hi. Mm-hmm!
干得好 小杀手
爸爸也要大开杀戒了
曼哈顿 下东区 D大道
嘿哟 西装佬
Hey yo, Waxy Boy!
西装佬 我把你要的箱子带来了
Waxy Boy, I got your box!
噢
Oh!
这里面到底有什么 你们这些白人
What you got there, white boy?
翻译：小P Bunny 冬可可     校对：Jophy
后期：hhjie     时间轴：阿黎     总监：Jophy
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
官方合作贴吧：百度《美剧血族》吧
百度《美剧血族》吧
血族
第一季  第二集
肯尼迪机场 货物D区
证件上写着他的名字是彼得毕晓普
His lanyard says his name is Peter Bishop,
航空交通管制的主管 你认识他吗
an ATC supervisor. You knew him?
他的头哪去了
Where is his head?
这就是他的头
That is his head.
我以为你们早就习惯这种场面了
I thought you guys were used to shit like this.
他不是医生
He's not a doctor.
要把他的头骨压碎到
It would take a lot of pressure
这种程度得要很大压力才行 是什么造成的
to crush his skull like that. What did this?
塔台说他是和你一起下来的
The tower said he came down here with you.
他在帮我们找一个里吉斯航空753
He was helping us look for a large cabinet
航班上的大柜子 那个柜子不见了
from Regis 753 that went missing.
里面有什么
What was in it?
我们认为是一些类似致病原的东西
We think it was some sort of infectious agent.
你是说就是那东西杀死了飞机上的人
You mean whatever killed the people on that plane?
我们还不知道
We don't know that.
现在一切只是理论 是吧
I mean, it's just a theory at this point. Right?
氨的味道
Ammonia.
-跟飞机上的一样 -你们有谁带着紫外线灯的吗
- Just like on the plane. - Hey, one of you got an ALS?
把工作灯关掉
Kill the work lights.
这是什么
What is that stuff?
某种生物的排泄物
Biological discharge.
跟鸟粪差不多
Closest analogue is guano.
或者是虱子的 那只虱子得有多大
That or tick shit. That's one hell of a tick.
我是古德温泽
Goodweather.
金 你怎么了
Jim, what's the matter with you?
整整一夜 没睡过 估计是咖啡喝太多了
Long night. No sleep. Maybe too much coffee.
该死 我不在乎他们说什么 给我拦住他们
Goddamn it! I don't care what he said! Just stall them.
脱光他们的衣服 什么都行 把他们拖住
Lose their clothes. I don't care, just keep them there
直到我过去 我们得走了
till we get there. We have to go.
疾控中心接管了这个现场
This crime scene is now under CDC authority.
任何人都不能碰那个尸体
Nobody touches that body.
巴尔内斯刚把那四个幸存者放了
Barnes just released the four survivors.
肯尼迪机场 疾控中心临时隔离区
你不用打的 我的司机会送你过去
You don't need a cab. My driver will drop you off.
很抱歉 各位 你们不能离开
I'm sorry, folks, but you're not going anywhere.
你就别白费力气了
Spare yourself the crucifixion.
你别想留住我们
You don't have a chance in hell of making that stick.
你现在还以为这是什么超级流感吗 医生
You still think it's some super flu, Doc?
你没看新闻吗
Haven't you seen the news?
有人把里吉斯航空的报告泄露到网上了
Someone leaked the Regis Air documents to the internet.
只是一氧化碳中毒 但是被航空公司总裁
It's carbon monoxide poisoning. All of it covered up
丹尼尔 弗拉克斯敦 隐瞒了
by the airline's CEO, Daniel Flaxton.
你可以安心了 医生
You should be relieved, Doctor.
已经不关你的事了 现在你不介意的话
It's out of your hands. Now if you don't mind,
-我还得去提出诉讼了 -你相信电视里说的一切
- I've got a lawsuit to file. - You believe everything on TV?
天哪 这人好烦 我们没事
Holy Jesus, is this man annoying. We're fine.
我们都很好 就不谢谢你了 医生
We're all fine. No thanks to you, Doc.
现在感觉没事不表示你们没病
Feeling fine at this moment does not mean you're not sick.
-有些病是有潜伏期的 -我知道了
- Diseases incubate. - Look, I get it.
这是你受尽万众瞩目
This is your time in the spotlight.
升职加薪的好机会 我们很乐意帮你
To snag a promotion. Love to help,
但是我在日蚀那天有个演唱会 所以
but I've got a major concert on the day of the eclipse, so...
我得走了 真的
I need to go. I do.
如果由我来决定的话 我想留下
If it were up to me, I'd stay,
但是我的律师要我出去 所以
but my union lawyers want me out, so...
别绕圈子了 我现在把话说清楚
We're going around in circles here. Let me be very clear:
你们都在我的命令下被隔离在这
you're all staying here under quarantine on my authority.
巴尔内斯局长说过我们可以走的
Director Barnes said we would be released.
我说你们得留下 不管他怎么说
And I say you stay. I don't care what Barnes said.
根据健康权利法案
According to the Health Powers Act,
只要有两个医师同意 隔离指令就可以生效
it only takes two physicians to issue a quarantine order.
想要来真的吗 我打个电话就可以让你丢掉工作
It's on. One phone call, I get your job.
-还有马菲特小姐也一样 -现在赶紧打
- And Little Miss Muffet's. - You better start dialing then.
在打了 凯特 我是琼 帮我接通卫生与公众服务部
Dialing. Katie, it's Joan. Get me the Secretary of Health
部长 格丽特皮尔森 的电话
and Human Services, Margaret Pierson.
在昨晚的新闻发布会上
At a press conference last night,
纽约的疾控中心首席医疗官
Dr. Ephraim Goodweather, chief medical officer
伊弗雷姆古德温泽博士
with the Centers for Disease Control in New York City,
石心集团
曼哈顿 第55街西 156号
说现在给他的调查
said it was too early
-下结论还过早 -这可是个麻烦啊
- in his investigation... - This could be a problem.
疾控中心封锁了机场
The CDC has closed the airport.
他们还没释放生还者
They have still not released the survivors.
如果他们继续把这个当成传染病
If they continue to treat this as an epidemic,
-我们的时间可能会被拖延 -一个小时后
- it will delay our timetable. - In an hour,
没有人会再说传染病这回事
nobody will be talking about an epidemic.
四个生还者也能出来了
And I'll have the four survivors on the street.
怎么做到
You will accomplish this how?
提供虚假情报
Disinformation.
一个好故事往往比事实更容易被接受
A good story always trumps the truth.
只需要给媒体一个攻击对象就行了
Just give the press a villain to hate.
现在 既然这事解决了
Now that this is done,
我什么时候能见他
when do I see him?
很快了
Soon.
他已经过河了 这是我们约定好的
He's across the river. That was our deal.
你很快就能见到他
You will see him soon.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
去见个老朋友
To see an old friend.
我已经读完了里吉斯航空
I personally read all 250 pages
250页的报告
of the Regis documents.
我对航空公司
And I was shocked
不顾乘客安全
by the airline's flagrant disregard
的行为感到震惊
for the safety of its passengers.
亚拉伯罕 赛特拉基安
Abraham Setrakian.
你的律师来见你了
Your lawyer's here to see you.
我没有律师
I have no lawyer.
你老了
You've grown old,
A230385
A230385.
艾霍斯特
Eichorst...
-见到我惊讶吗 -都这么多年了
- Surprised to see me? - It has been many years.
你看起来还是那个样子
You look exactly the same.
你的心跳乱了 我能听出来 犹太人
Your heartbeat is irregular. I can hear it, Jew,
像钟声一样清楚
clear as a bell.
棺材过河了吗
Did the coffin cross the river?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
你的主人现在在哪呢
And where is your Master now?
他在通过我看着你
Watching you through me.
犹太人 游戏结束了
The great game is over, Jew.
只要我还有一口气在 就不会让游戏结束
Not while I still breathe.
真厉害
Amazing.
尽管所有证据都显示你会失败
Despite all evidence to the contrary,
你还是坚信
you cling to the delusion
你会成功
that you will prevail.
别跟我说你还相信
Don't tell me you still believe
你们的神
in that God of yours.
他现在在哪
So where is He?
为何他毫无动静
Why has He done nothing?
面对现实吧
Face the truth.
他只是你们虚构出来的
He is nothing but a figment of your imagination.
你的逮捕报告里说你被捕的时候
Your arrest report says you were apprehended
身上带有一把古剑
with an antique sword.
-是萨都的剑吗 -不用担心
- Is it Sardu's? - Don't worry.
我会在适当的时候还给你的主人的
I will give it back to your Master in due time.
真有趣
That is amusing.
还有她的心脏
And her heart...
你现在还保留着吗
Do you still have that as well?
你还真多愁善感呢
Oh, you are such a sentimentalist.
你可能很想知道这个
You might like to know this.
她到死都在反抗
She struggled at the very end,
但是她没哭出来
but she never cried out.
很奇怪 连啜泣都没有
I thought that strange. Not even a whimper.
只是一直喊着
Only a single word.
亚拉伯罕
"Abraham."
但是你不在那
But you were not there
帮不了她
to help her.
你后悔吗
Do you feel great regret?
我会替她报仇的
I will avenge her.
你什么仇都报不了
You will not avenge anyone.
你不是英雄 也不是救世主
You're not a hero or a savior.
你只是一个编号
You're just a number.
我拿走了你的名字 给了你一个编号
I took your name and gave you that number.
这是你所有的东西了
That's all you are.
对你来说呆在这里是一件好事
It's good for you that you are in here.
这是唯一能让你有安全感的地方了
It's the only place you can feel safe.
比在大街上还安全
Safer than the streets will be very soon.
你可以
You might survive
活久一点
a little longer.
我要你
I want you
眼睁睁看着事情发生
to watch it unfold, unable to do anything
却无能为力
to stop it.
你死之前
And when you die,
最后看到的东西
it will be the Master's eyes
将会是我主人的眼睛
you see last...
还记得你的老朋友
Remember your old friend,
德雷福希文吗
Dreverhaven?
你想知道为什么他不能在这
Would you like to know why
和你一起共享此刻的荣耀吗
he isn't here to share your glory with you?
因为我用那把剑把他碎尸万段了
Because I cut him to pieces with that sword
然后将尸体
and dumped his parts
扔进了北海
in the North Sea.
我相信 你们很快就可以
I'll see that you're reunited with him
团聚了
very soon.
走着瞧吧
Until next time...
A230385
A230385.
曼哈顿 哈莱姆区 东115街
妈妈 我回来了
Mama, I home!
她正准备做弥撒
She's getting ready for Mass.
为什你不收拾一下你的东西
Why don't you clean your shit up?
不要说话 看
Shh! Listen.
-飞机满载着尸体回来了 -我说什么来着
- Plane coming in wit those stiffs on it? - What did I say?
嗯
Huh?
-你以为我是在和你说着玩吗 -回来了 儿子
- You think I'm playing with you? - Hola, mijo.
妈妈
Hola, mami!
你好吗  你看起来漂亮极了
Como estas? Mira, que linda! You look beautiful.
你看起来 糟透了
You look... terrible.
儿子 我不喜欢你像这样
Oh, mijo. I don't like you
工作到这么晚 这对你不好
working nights like this. It's not good for you.
-我知道 -和我一起去弥撒
- I know. - Come to Mass with me.
科特斯神父一直问起你
Father Cortez has been asking about you.
我去不了 妈妈 我要去睡觉了
I can't, Mama, I gotta get some sleep.
下星期吧
Next week.
你看到克里斯宾给我的东西了吗
Did you see what Crispin got me?
不 我没看见
No, I didn't see it.
哇哦
Wow...
这东西可真不错 你从哪弄来的 兄弟
That's a nice piece. Where'd you get it, bro?
跳蚤市场
Flea market.
便宜得跟白捡的那样 那个老女人不知道她这东西是啥
Was a real steal. Old lady didn't know what she had.
很高兴我的两个孩子又聚到一起
So good to have my two kids together again.
你们今晚都会在这吃饭吧
Your both will here for dinner?
-是的 妈妈 -我要做点特别的菜
- Si, Mama. - I'll make something special.
-好的 -拜拜
- OK. - Bye!
-拜拜 妈妈 我爱你 -我也爱你
- Bye, Mommy, I love you. - I love you too!
你从哪得到这个的
Where'd you get it? Huh?
你从哪得到这个的 说实话 你个废物
Where d'you get it? The truth, you junkie piece of shit!
说啊 说啊
Huh? Huh?
离这几个街区的那间当铺 那个买银器的犹太人
The pawn shop a couple blocks down! The Jew who buys silver.
你别把偷回来的垃圾带进这房子里
You don't bring stolen shit into this house
-还把妈妈拉下水 -好的
- and involve Mom on it. - OK!
-你听到了吗 -听到了
- You hear me? - Yes!
你知道吗 格斯 你竟然还有胆量
You know, Gus, you got some balls
和我这样说话
talking to me like that.
两年了
Two years.
你在北部的这两年来 我听着她
Two years I listened to her cry herself to sleep at night
每晚哭着入睡
while you were upstate.
我才是唯一一个陪着她的人
I was the only one who was here for her!
你拿着她的血汗钱买药嗑
You were shooting her paychecks up your arm.
-好吧 被你说中了 -是啊 我说中了
- OK, you got me. - Yeah, I got you.
好啊 那你呢 格斯
OK. But what about you, Gus, huh?
-我什么 -距离下次你再被逮住
- What about me? - How you long is it gonna be
再伤透她的心还要多久 哼？
before you get busted again and break her heart? Huh?
我要把这钟还回去
I'm taking this clock back.
那也洗不掉你的罪恶 大圣人
That's not gonna wash you clean , altar boy!
你反驳了我的明确指令
You contradicted my explicit orders
肯尼迪机场 疾控中心临时指挥所
还宣称要对他们进行隔离检疫
and declared them quarantined.
你不能放了这些幸存者
You can't release those survivors.
除非我们弄清楚我们面对着的是什么
Not till we know what we're facing.
我们很清楚 让我给你介绍
We do know. Let me introduce you
卫生与公众服务部的部长
to the Secretarof Health and Human Services,
玛格丽特·皮尔森
Margaret Pierson.
很高兴见到你 古德温泽博士
Pleasure to meet you, Dr. Goodweather.
马丁内兹博士 让我向你们讲一下最新情况
Dr. Martinez. Let me bring you both up to speed.
这些里吉斯航空的报告
These Regis Air documents
指出了航班753上出现了一个系统故障
point to a systems failure aboard flight 753.
所以我已经让联邦航空局禁飞了里吉斯航空的全部航线
So I've had the FAA ground the entire Regis Airline fleet
直到国家运输安全委员会完成调查
until the NTSB completes its investigation.
这不仅仅是疾控中心的案子了
It's not a CDC case anymore.
国家运输安全委员会已经接受这个案子了
The NTSB has the ball now.
恕我直言 部长
With all due respect, Madam Secretary,
这些人不是死于一个航空系统故障
these people didn't die from a faulty air system.
-不是吗 -我调查出来的所有线索
- They didn't? - Everything in my investigation
都指向一种致命的病原体
points to a virulent pathogen.
我们远远没有弄清到底发生什么事情
We're far from understanding exactly what did happen,
但我们需要关闭这个机场以防止它传播
but we need to shut down this airport so it doesn't spread.
-伊弗 冷静 -古德温泽博士
- Eph, please. - Dr. Goodweather,
我很欣赏你的热情
I appreciate ur zeal.
但你需要往后退一步 好好考虑一下
But you need to step back for a moment and consider
医疗检疫的影响
the impact of a medical quarantine.
那会致使纽约通向世界各地的
It would immediately stop all exports
所有出口贸易立即停止
from New York to he rest of the world.
单凭一个预感 你就想要断送70亿的经济贸易
Do you want to crash a $70 billion economy
让股票市场来一次自由落体吗
and send the stock markets into a free fall on a hunch?
伊弗 我知道你在你的个人生活中
Eph, I know you've been under a lot of stress
一直都承受着很大压力 这是很主要的原因
in your personal life, that's a big part of the cause.
-但不要把你的负担 -我的个人生活
- But don't bring your baggage... - My personal life
和这个没有一点关系 这关乎救人性命
has nothing to do with this. It's about saving people.
就是那么简单 伊弗
It's that simple. Eph...
抱歉 艾弗雷特 我不应该那么做
Sorry, Everett. I shouldn't have done that.
对 你不应该
No, you shouldn't have.
接下来这样
Here's what's going to happen.
你要放几天假
You're going to take a few days off.
然后等这件事一平息 我们再来讨论
Then once this all blows over, we're going to revisit
你的情况 而现在  这件事与你无关了
your situation. As now, you're no longer involve.
回家吧
Go home.
您好 这里是纽约
You've reached the office
首席法医的办公室
of the Chief Medical Examiner of New York City.
暂时无人接
No one is available to take...
我找不到班尼特 或者是任何人
I can't reach Bennett, or anybody.
他们就不能接下法医办公室的电话吗
Why aren't they picking up at the coroner's office?
他们手上有206个尸体 他们估计有点忙
They got 206 dead bodies, they're probably a little busy.
皇后区霍华德海滩 科尔曼广场
雷德芬机长 感谢你愿意见我们
Captain Redfern? Thanks for agreeing to meet us.
没事
You bet.
我的乘客和机务人员都相信我能把他们安全带到肯尼迪国际机场
My passengers and crew trusted me to get them to JFK safely.
但我没做到 我想知道为什么
But I didn't. I'd like to know why.
你看起来有点苍白
You look a little pale.
我没事 只是有点头痛
I'm OK. A bit of a headache.
耳朵有点耳鸣
There's that humming in my ears.
我们的确有一个非医学上的问题想问你
We do have a non-medical question for you.
有一大件货物从飞机上失踪了
A large piece of cargo has gone missing from the plane.
那个箱子
the box
你知道那箱子的事吗
You know about the box?
我当时在机上做起飞前的巡查
I was doing my pre-flight walk around on the plane.
四个穿着制服的官员
Four officials in suits show up
坐着政府用车 带着这大箱子出现
in a government van with this huge crate.
我们之前也运送过紧急的高级机密货物
We've carried last-minute high- security cargo in the past,
所以我也没多想
so I didn't think much of it.
这个箱子 是不是9×4英尺
This box, it was maybe nine foot by four foot?
是的
Yes.
你知道是什么政府部门吗 他们是谁
Do you know what government office? Who they were?
他们下车后从停机坪走上我的飞机
They got down onto the tarmac to my plane,
他们穿着制服 带着徽章
they had suits and badges...
我知道这一定是公务员
I figured it had to be official.
但我有什么资格去质问呢
Who am I to question this?
但就是因为我没有去问
But because I didn't,
206个人死了
206 people are dead.
其他人依然有危险 但你能救他们
Other people are still in danger. You can help save them.
你可以去圣塞巴斯蒂安的
Here's what you can do: go to the emergency room
急救室
at St. Sebastian's.
有位威廉姆·莱斯特医生会在那接见你
A Dr. William Lester will meet you there.
他是谁
Who's he?
他是我所认识的最好的诊断专家
He's the best diagnostician I know.
他会将你当作私人病患进行收治
He'll admit you as a private patient,
算是帮我个忙 做一些检测
as a favor to me, and run some tests.
他会找到是什么原因导致你的耳鸣
He'll find out what's causing the sound in your ears
-和头痛 -好的
- and your headaches. - OK.
真是难以置信 这么费劲地折腾
Unbelievable. Jumping through all these hoops
就是因为那些混蛋不愿意进行检疫隔离
because those bastards don't want to face a quarantine.
航空公司怕承担责任
And the airline's worried about their liability,
我的工会也是
my union is worried about theirs...
每个人的头等大事
Everyone's first priority
都是保障自身
is covering their asses.
没有一个人在乎真相
And no one gives a shit about the truth.
我在乎 你也在乎
I do, and you do,
而这是现在我们最大的筹码
and that's the best shot we've got right now.
哦 我的天哪
Oh, my God...
它的口腔有锯齿状的突起物
Its buccal cavity has serrated projections.
所以它能抓住或者刺穿任何组织
So it can latch onto or cut through tissue.
我想试点东西
I want to try something.
得快点
Make it quick.
在我们被盘问之前搞定
Before someone asks what the hell we're doing here.
如果这些寄生虫真的感染了受害者
If these worms did infect the victims,
向性反应是一种生物学现象 指生物受环境因素刺激而向某特定方向移动或生长
那么人类血液就会产生一种向性反应
then human blood should produce a tropic reaction.
快看那个
Look at that...
爸爸 你还好吗：（ 担心你  ——扎克
今晚事儿太多了 去睡吧 宝贝 明天打给你 爱你 ——爸爸
今天你会过来吗
是扎克 我应该过去谈谈
It's Zack. I'm supposed to stop by to talk about
-监护权听证会的事了 -你最好过去
- the custody hearing. - You better go then.
不了 这更重要 他会理解的
No, this is important. He'll understand.
他会理解成他并没有你的工作重要
He'll understand he's not as important as your work,
这也正是他每天所听到他妈妈说的话
which is exactly what he hears from his mother every day.
你想要法官把完全监护权判给凯莉吗
You want the judge to give Kelly full custody?
当然不想
Of course not.
那就去啊
Take a moment.
雷德芬的检测结果没几个小时是出不来的
Redfern's test results won't come in for a couple of hours.
我会搞定这个的
I'll finish this.
谢谢你
Thank you.
医院见
See you at the hospital.
曼哈顿14街 西547号
-你在这里做什么 -瓦西里·费特
- What are you doing in here? - Vasiliy Fet.
-城市害虫控制中心的检察员 -周日也来吗
- Inspector, City Pest Control. - On a Sunday?
不 你现在不能进行检查
No! You're not doing an inspection now.
我们没时间 这是我们的香槟早午餐时间
There's no time... this is our champagne brunch.
一周内最忙的服务时段
Busiest service of the week.
-抱歉 我们收到投诉 -你想要吃早餐吗
- Sorry. We had a complaint. - You want breakfast?
跟厨师点餐就好
Give the order to one of the line chefs.
但我不会给你任何现金
But I am not giving you any cash.
你以为我到这来就为了这个吗
Is that what you think I'm here for?
哈 看
Ha! Look.
看到那个了吗
You see that?
那是鼠尿
That's rat urine.
真是荒谬 好吧
Ridiculous! OK,
两百美元 你立刻给我滚出去
two hundred dollars, but you get the hell out of here right now.
-不 -这会是个错误的决定
- No. - You're making a big mistake.
我做过很多错误的决定 但从没断错过害虫
I make many mistakes, but not about vermin.
走开
Move.
那可是个价值3百万的
That was a $300,000 offer
30分钟的视频采访邀请
for a 30-minute on-camera interview.
-而你就这样挂了电话 -不管他们开出什么条件
- And you hang up?! - Whatever they're offering,
跟我们从航空公司拿到的
it's gonna be chump change
比起来 都不算什么
compared to what we'll get from the airline.
这可能会被归类于 一夜爆红
This may go in the category of "Too soon,"
但销量却一路飙升
but ticket sales are way up.
我就爱你这点 鲁比
That's what I love about you, Ruby.
敬大难不死
Here's to being alive.
作为一个艺术家 在这样的时刻
Moments like this... As an artist,
这样的事情让你后退一步
they make you take a step back
-静观大局 -去质问 为何是我们
- and look at the big picture. - There's no answer
是没有答案的只不过是运气好点  但我欣然接受
to "Why us." It's just random luck, but I'll take it.
-又来了 哼鸣声
- - There's that... hum again.
你也能听到 对吗
You hear it still, don't you?
就像是回声一样
It's almost like an echo.
像是某种声音的回响
Like an echo of a voice,
可能是当你耳朵或者鼻子堵住的时候 听到的你自己的声音
maybe your own voice, when your ears and nose are stuffed.
-真奇怪 -我没听到
- It's weird. - I'm not hearing it,
不过加布 如果那声音有曲调 记得写下来
but Gabe, if that voice has a tune, write it down.
这让我想起我的第一次迷幻之旅
Reminds me of my first acid trip.
你嗑过迷幻药吗 琼
You ever done acid, Joan?
没 没嗑过
Nope, no acid.
迷幻药不是我的菜
Not my thing.
什么才是你的菜
What is your thing?
想要去别的地方嗨皮吗
You want to take this party someplace else?
比如说
Like?
我新影院上面的联排别墅
Townhouse above my new theater.
我们可以庆祝
We can celebrate
我们逃过一劫
our escape from the abyss.
不了 我还是回家吧
No, I better get home
去见见我的孩子们 还有我的丈夫
and see my kids. And my husband.
不如下次吧
Maybe another time?
我明天要去公司和我们的法律团队汇合
I'm going to be getting together our legal team
我们很快会再见面的 加布
at the firm tomorrow. We'll talk soon, Gabe.
我得放松一下 鲁比
I need to get my pipes cleaned, Ruby.
挑几个身材火辣的
Pick out a couple of hot ones.
所有人都停下手中的工作
Everyone stop what they're doing.
不要再把食物端出厨房了
No more food goes out of the kitchen.
现在 赶紧开始打扫清理
As of right now, you start cleaning...
如果你们还想重新开业的话
if you ever want this place to open up again.
你不能让我们关门
You can't shut us down!
香卡议员每周三都会来这里用餐
Councilwoman Shankar eats here every Wednesday.
是吗 那你打算给他吃这个喽
Oh yeah? You gonna serve her this?
各位 请注意
Attention, everybody!
卫生部门已经下令
By order of the health department, this establishment
将这餐厅关闭 清楚了吗
is now closed. All right?
所有人都出去
Everyone must leave.
嗨 亲爱的
Hey, hon.
赶紧走吧
Time to go!
看来我们不用付钱了
I'm guessing we don't have to pay.
曼哈顿 第57街西 156号
莫西医生带来了好消息 先生
Dr. Moise called with some good news, sir.
新肝脏又强壮又健康 是一个工人的
The liver's young and healthy. It belongs to a laborer.
他没有亲人 不会被人发现
No family. He won't be missed.
莫西想尽快把它给移植
Moise would like to move ahead with the acquisition.
我还不确定我是否需要用它
I'm not sure I'll need it anymore.
请恕我直言 先生
With all due respect, sir,
如果这些人不能履行他们的承诺的话
if these other people can't deliver what they've promised...
他们会履行的 马上
They can. And they will.
即便如此 您也应该以防万一
Even so, you should have a backup.
您要知道 飞到波哥大要五个小时
Keep in mind: it's a five-hour flight to Bogota.
去取肝脏至少得要八个小时
Minimum of eight hours to harvest the organ.
现在又要多花五个小时飞回来
Five more to return.
您的肝脏功能已经异常衰竭了
Your liver functionality is already well below normal.
随时都可能出状况 如果真的发生什么
It could fail at any time. If it does fail,
您会有生命危险的
it will be a challenge to keep you alive
除非已经换了新的肝脏
until we receive the replacement.
好了 我知道了
All right. Fine.
- 那就做吧 - 我觉得离开这栋楼
- Do it. - I'm not sure it's wise
不太明智 先生 感染会
to leave the building, sir. Infection will--
对我承担手术的能力不利
Adversely affect my ability to withstand surgery.
是的 我知道 我要走了
Yes, yes, yes. I'm going.
不用再多说什么了
There is no debate.
事实上 我一生中从来没有像这次一样
In fact, I've never felt more excited about a meeting
对接下来的会面如此激动过
in my entire life.
皇后区 伍德赛德 凯尔顿街
我也这么觉得 诺拉 101华氏度没有什么好紧张的
I agree, Nora: 101 degrees is not cause for alarm,
不过我也不希望他的体温继续上升
but I don't like that his temperature's rising.
好的 等雷德芬的报告出来了
Fine. I'll meet you back at the hospital by the time
我再去医院找你
Redfern's path report gets back.
好的
Good.
等会联系 抱歉
Talk soon. Sorry.
- 是关于飞机事件 - 嗯 我也一直关注着
- It's the airplane case. - Yeah, I've been watching.
但为什么你会牵扯进去
But why are you involved?
他们说那架飞机有问题
They say something was wrong with the plane.
完全是胡说八道 没有人想要得到真相
That's total bullshit. Nobody wants to deal with the truth.
真相是什么
What is it?
我不知道
I don't know.
还没进展
Nothing's adding up.
- 这也太可怕了 - 没错
- That's scary. - It is.
我很庆幸是你在处理
Well, I'm glad you're handling it.
这意味着无论是什么问题都会被解决
That means whatever needs to be done will get done.
谢谢
Thank you.
哦 进来吧
Oh, come in.
马特在里面
Matt's here.
- 嗨 伊弗 - 嗨
- Hey, Eph. - Hey...
戴安 我叫戴安 我和你见过差不多
Diane. My name's Diane. I've met you,
有五次了 我每隔一天会开车送你孩子上学
five times. I drive your kid to school every other day,
你都还记不住我的名字
and you can't even remember my name.
我记得你的名字 戴安 刚刚只是没有想起来
I remember your name, Diane. I just drew a blank.
真有趣 对你我颗可从来没有想不起来过
Funny, I've never drawn a blank about you.
一次也没有 为什么呢 伊弗
Not once. Why is that, Eph?
戴安 扎克在后面
Diane. Zack's in the back,
- 帮马特的忙 - 在干什么
- helping Matt. - Do what?
我们正在把你的老办公室
We're converting your old office
改造成游戏室
into a game room.
嗨 爸爸
Hey, Dad.
- 嗨 扎克 - 最近怎样 伊弗
- Hey, Zack. - How's it going, Eph?
还行
Ok.
所以你们在重建这间房
So you're rebuilding this place, huh?
没错 这里放一台
Yeah. Giant screen TV
巨型银幕电视 放在这个房间里刚刚好
over here. Perfect size for a room like this.
音响放这里 还有这里
Speakers here, and here.
这里会变得焕然一新
This'll be a great new space for us.
听着 我知道这样很尴尬
Listen... I know this is awkward,
但我不太希望这样
but I don't want it to be.
呃
Um...
让她幸福就好
Just make her happy.
让他们都过得幸福 除此之外别无所求
Just make them happy. That's all I ask.
放心吧
You got it.
哦 哦 好吧
Oh. Oh, OK.
很好
Great.
我能和我儿子说几句话吗
Mind if I speak with my son?
当然可以 我打赌 过段时间
No, of course. You know, in time,
我们会成为很好的朋友
I bet you and I will become good friends.
有可能
Maybe.
嗨 扎克 扎克 我马上要走了
Hey, Zack, Zack, I gotta go.
因为那架飞机的事 我知道
Because of that plane. I know.
我想跟你谈谈
I wanted to talk about
- 明天的监护权听证会 - 行
- the custody hearing tomorrow. - OK.
- 别迟到就行了 - 不会的 一定不会的
- Just don't be late. - I won't. I won't be.
- 我发誓 - 你想谈什么
- I mean it. - So what about it?
呃
Uh...
对我们来说 会是个尴尬的场合 对吧
It is a weird situation, huh, for all of us?
妈妈说法官会问各种问题
Mom says the judge will ask all kinds of questions.
是的 他会的 也可能是个女的问 不管是谁反正都会问的
Yeah, he will. Or she will. Whoever it is, they will.
你想好怎么说了吗
Have you thought about what you were gonna say?
妈妈说我怎么想就怎么说
Mom says I should just say how I feel.
那是当然 就按照你内心的想法说
Absolutely. Just be honest. Just from your heart.
- 你打算怎么说 - 我 和你一样
- What are you gonna say? - Me? Same thing.
就说些我的想法 我会说
My feelings. I'm gonna say
你是这个世界上对我来说
you're the most important person
最重要的人 因为这就是事实
in the world to me, because you are,
- 还会说我想要共同抚养权 - 那是什么
- and that I want joint custody. - What's that?
意思是
That means...
你和我相处的时间
that you get to spend as much time with me
跟你和妈妈相处的时间一样多
as you do with your mother.
你也是这么想的 对吧
And I know that's what you want, right?
嗯 但是如果你老是这么忙
Yeah... But if you're always so busy...
不会的 等这次事件解决之后一定不会了
I won't be, not after I put this case to bed.
你老是这么说 我知道你是认真的
You always say that. And I know you mean it,
- 但从来没实现过 - 扎克 扎克 看着我
- but it's never true. - Zack, Zack, look at me...
这一次
This time,
我一定说到做到
it will be.
皇后区 阿斯托里亚 31街
我以为你不会来
I didn't think you were gonna show.
履行承诺是
Keeping commitments is...
治疗过程的一部分
Is part of my recovery process.
嗨 我叫伊弗
Hi, my name's Eph.
我是酗酒者
I'm an alcoholic.
我已经一年零十一天
I've been sober one year
没有沾酒了
and eleven days.
正在接受治疗
I'm in therapy.
试着认清自己
Learning about myself.
这是一趟漫长的旅行
It's a journey of discovery. Uh...
医生说我兼具被动和主动攻击性性格
I'm passive-aggressive and actively aggressive,
这很少见 他们是这么跟我说的
which is a rare combination, I'm told.
让我想想 还有什么 我是控制狂 以自我为中心
Let's see, what else? I'm controlling. I'm self-centered.
和家人感情疏远
I'm emotionally distant for my family.
噢 还有最坏的一点
Oh, and the greatest sin of all:
我爱工作
I love my work.
但这些我都认了 因为都是我应得的
But I'm taking it all in, you know, I'm owning it.
这对我产生了很大的影响
And it's really making a difference.
我的妻子要和我离婚
My wife's divorcing me,
和另外一个家伙搞上了
and screwing this new dude...
就在我的房子 我的房间里
in my bed. In my house,
房子的房贷甚至还是我在还着
on which I'm still making payments.
老毛病又犯了 是吧 理查德 我的担保人说
There I go again, right, Richard? My sponsor says
我总是用讽刺的方式来逃避真实情感
that I use sarcasm to avoid my real feelings,
因为如果我是真心爱凯利 我会替她感到高兴
that if I truly loved Kelly, I would be happy for her,
而不是憎恨她
I wouldn't resent her...
我已经努力了 理查德
I'm trying, Richard.
但我走得很艰难
But it is a very steep hill.
就在我来之前我才见过他们
I saw them right before I came here.
他们三个在一起
All three of them together.
做着我一直都没有时间去做的事
Doing things I never had time to do,
到现在我都没时间去做
still don't have time to do...
我想喝一杯
I wanted a drink.
我走之后经过了一家酒吧
I passed a bar after I left there.
但我还是来到了这里
But I came here.
因为我不能失去扎克
Because I can't blow it with Zack.
因为他是我剩下的唯一了
Cuz that I have left.
他就是我的全部
He's my whole world.
准备好狂欢了吗
Are you ready to party with me?
当然
Yeah!
你闻起来真香 尝起来肯定更好美味
You smell beautiful. I bet you taste even better.
- 你没事吧 加布 - 没事 没事
- You okay, Gabe? - Yeah, yeah.
我还没从德国时差缓过来
I'm still on German time.
继续不要停 我马上就进入状态
Keep the beat going. I'll catch up.
你咬我 你这混蛋
You bit me, you bastard!
- 狗屎 - 我流血了 他真咬了我
- Bullshit. - I'm bleeding. He bit me hard!
滚出去
Get out.
快滚
Get out! Out!
滚 你疯了
Out! You're crazy!
皇后区 圣塞巴斯蒂安医院
情况怎样
What's wrong?
雷德芬刚刚失去了控制
Redfern just went into a tailspin.
莱斯特和他在一起 这是病情报告
Lester's with him. Here's the path report.
从没见过这种情况
I've never seen anything like it.
太不可思议了 畸变器官 外来细胞
This is crazy: Aberrant, foreign cells...
多型核现象
nuclear pleomorphism.
双表型外观 就像有什么东西
Biphenotypic appearance... It's like something
强行占领了他的细胞组织
shanghaied his cellular machinery
并正在制造着完全不一样的东西
and is creating something totally different.
我们已经抑制了他的疼痛和初期流感 不过
We've sedated him for the pain, started fluids, but...
- 抗体报告送过来没有 - 没有
- Antibody studies back in yet? - No.
- 感觉怎么样 多伊尔 - 全身沸腾
- How you feeling, Doyle? - Boiling.
皮肤有什么在爬行 感觉像吞了一把剃刀 用紫外光
Skin's crawling. I feel like I swallowed a razor. UV light.
小心眼睛
Watch your eyes.
伤疤 和航班其他受害者一样的地方
A scar. Same place as the airline victims.
只是它恢复太快
It just healed so fast
没有紫外光照射根本看不见
we couldn't see it without UV light.
伊弗 看
Eph, look!
金 找到巴恩斯 告诉他雷德芬情况变严峻了
Jim, find Barnes. Tell him that Redfern's gone critical.
他发现你在治疗雷德芬的话
He's gonna be really pissed when he finds out
肯定会非常生气 没空管这个 告诉他
you've been treating him. I don't give a shit! Tell him
有一个幸存者现在非常虚弱
that one of the survivors is very sick.
还有我们需要召回剩下的幸存者
Tell him we need to corral the rest of the survivors
以及一切和他们接触过的人
and anybody they've had contact with.
现在就去 好的
Now. Yes, sir.
解剖室现在应该有些成果了
The autopsies should have turned something up by now.
班尼特医生还是不接电话
Dr. Bennett is still not answering.
又直接转入语音箱了
It went straight to voice mail again.
好吧 如果到现在还无动于衷的话
Well, if the mountain won't come to Mahomet...
那我们直接去停尸房
We're going to the morgue.
古德温泽博士 我是疾控中心站的劳里
Dr. Goodweather? This is Laurie from the CDC exchange.
- 有一个叫加里阿诺特的打了过来 - 好的
- There's a Gary Arnot calling. - Yeah, OK.
你好 是医生吗
Hello? Yes, Doctor,
我是加里阿诺特
this is Gary Arnot.
- 我是艾玛的 - 我知道你是谁 阿诺特先生
- I'm Emma's... - I know who you are, Mr. Arnot.
首先 我想为我之前做的事情
First of all, I just wanted to say
皇后区牙买加住宅区 都铎路
向你道歉
that I'm sorry for what I did,
还有 谢谢你把我的宝贝女儿送回了家
and to thank you for sending my little girl home to me.
什么 你是说有人把她的尸体送回去了
What? Are you saying someone released her body to you?
不 不是尸体
No, not her body.
艾玛还活着 今天早上她出现在家门口
Emma's alive. She showed up on my doorstep this morning.
呃 阿诺特先生 我有点糊涂了
Uh, Mr. Arnot, I'm a little confused.
- 你的意思是 - 你不相信我
- Are you telling me... - You don't believe me?
好吧 无所谓
You know what? Fine, whatever.
- 我只是 - 我女儿在家很安全
- I'm just trying to... - My daughter's home safe.
反正这才是最重要的 非常感谢你
That's all that matters. Thank you very much.
你觉得她可能还活着吗
Do you think it's possible she's alive?
他受了打击 看见的是幻觉
He's in shock. He's seeing ghosts.
当时我在座位上检查了她 她已经死了
I examined her in her seat, she's dead.
我们登上那架飞机的时候 每个人看起来都死了
When we boarded that plane, everybody looked dead.
然后四个人醒了过来
Then four of them woke up.
这些虫子会不会使人
Could these worms somehow induce
进入类似冬眠的状态
some sort of state of hibernation?
就像舌蝇
Like tsetse flies?
马上我们就会知道了
We'll find out in ten minutes.
如果她死了 她会在停尸房里
If she's dead, she'll be at the morgue.
先生
Sir?
我知道您不喜欢听
I know you don't wanna hear this,
但我跟随您很久了 听过很多医生
but I've been with you a long time and listened
对你许下各种各样的承诺
to a lot of doctors promise you a lot of things.
他们什么能做什么不能做 我都看在眼里
I've seen what can be done and what can't.
这些人 他们在欺骗你
These people... They're deceiving you.
这些人有一种
These people have power
你完全意想不到的能力
beyond anything you can imagine.
到时候 你也会从中受益的
In time, you also will benefit from that power.
留在车里
Stay with the car.
我必须一个人面对
I need to do this alone.
太阳已经落下了
The sun has fallen.
你很幸运 帕尔默先生
You are very fortunate, Mr. Palmer.
他选中你来见证这光荣的时刻
He has chosen you to bear witness to his glory.
欢迎来到新世界
Welcome to the New World.
你大老远把我带过来
You brought me all the way here.
都不打算看我一眼吗
Aren't you going to look at me?
你好 有人吗
Hello? Anybody here?
首席法医办公室
曼哈顿 东30街
班尼特医生
Dr. Bennett?
班尼特医生 你还好吗
Dr. Bennett, you OK?
禁区
严禁入内
有人吗
Hello?
袋子是空的 每个都是
Every bag is empty. Every single one.
是你把灯关了的吗
我抱你出来吧 水都凉了
要聊天的话 我可以跟你说
我会慢慢听你说
我待会儿放狮子王的曲子 我们一起吃饭
你饿了吗
饿了
来 先擦干
来
新浪微博@SSK字幕组·合作贴吧《美剧血族》吧
更多精彩内容敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
如果你对这部剧有什么看法请进入百度贴吧《美剧血族》吧